14	No new changes to save.
12	Create a fork
11	Working on it...
10	Test Results
10	Create a fork to save changes
8	Save request
8	Share request
8	Refresh results
8	Unsaved changes
8	Save request to a collection
8	Only requests saved in a collection can be shared. You need edit access to save requests.
8	This could be possibly due to security policies. Please contact your admin for further details or assistance.
8	You don't have permission to make changes to this collection. Fork the collection to your workspace to save changes.
7	Request Name
7	Save Request
7	Desktop Agent
7	Untitled Request
7	Add to Jira Cloud
7	Save changes to Postman & Github
6	Example Name
6	Example details
6	Request details
6	Create Fork & Save
6	Automatically follow redirects
6	There are no tests for this request
6	Select the HTTP version to use for sending the request.
5	New messages
5	All Messages
5	Response Size
5	Reload this page.
5	Pre-request Script
5	URL cannot be empty
5	Open post-response scripts
5	Schema editor failed to load
5	Open the site's permission settings.
5	Tests are now a part of post-response scripts
5	An unexpected error occurred while loading the schema editor.
5	Postman needs local network access enabled in your browser to connect with the Desktop Agent.
5	You can use scripts to write tests, pre-request scripts, visualize responses and bring a ton of automation to your API workflows.
4	Share feedback
4	Request timed out
4	Sending request...
4	Desktop Agent unavailable
4	Send request to get a response
4	Access to History revoked by Admin
4	You need Editor access on this collection to save an example.
4	You don't have permission to send requests in this workspace.
3	Send options
3	Save Response
3	Debug request
3	Schema Fetched
3	Restore Default
3	I'll do it later
3	Type a new method
3	Save as duplicate
3	Send and Download
3	Download response
3	Visualize response
3	Disable cookie jar
3	No request history
3	Save overrides only
3	Enter cipher suites
3	Script with Postbot
3	Switch request type
3	No cookies available
3	Switch to build mode
3	Switch to comment mode
3	Request method changed
3	Sign in to use schemas
3	Cipher suite selection
3	Continue writing tests
3	Enter URL or paste text
3	Explore API capabilities
3	Encode URL automatically
3	Get a successful response
3	Write and view tests here
3	Enable strict HTTP parser
3	Add tests to this request
3	Write scripts with Postbot
3	Follow original HTTP Method
3	Follow Authorization header
3	Request settings unavailable
3	Write scripts easily with AI
3	Interceptor Agent unavailable
3	Tip: Use ⌘S for quick saving.
3	Sign in to use Spec Hub schemas
3	Prompt Postbot to write scripts
3	Local network access unavailable
3	This request does not have a body
3	Remove referer header on redirect
3	Enable SSL certificate verification
3	A few more seconds and I'll be done...
3	You need to be online to view comments.
3	Follow HTTP 3xx responses as redirects.
3	Save your requests to avoid losing work
3	Use server cipher suite during handshake
3	Request Method contains invalid characters
3	Restrict responses with invalid HTTP headers.
3	Send the request and browse through its history.
3	Comment mode is unavailable for unsaved requests.
3	Remove the referer header when a redirect happens.
3	Define variables in JSON format to use in the query
3	Continue working with the last created request type
3	You need to save the request before it can be shared
3	Use JavaScript to configure this request dynamically.
3	Set a cap on the maximum number of redirects to follow.
3	It's a bad response! Write tests for this request anyway?
3	You don't have permission to save changes in this workspace.
3	Use JavaScript to write tests, visualize response, and more.
3	Fork this collection to your own workspace to send a request.
3	Upgrade to Enterprise plan to save overrides on linked requests.
3	Work across multiple API technologies using Postman’s API client.
3	Restore this setting to the default value used in global settings.
3	Encode the URL's path, query parameters, and authentication fields.
3	Make sure the Postman Interceptor extension is installed and enabled.
3	Use post-response scripts to write tests, visualize responses and do more.
3	You need to be online to use Spec Hub schemas for autocomplete suggestions.
3	Incorrect Schema. Autocomplete options related to the schema will not work.
3	Request method has been changed to POST for the selected body type - GraphQL
3	Retain authorization header when a redirect happens to a different hostname.
3	Use the server's cipher suite order instead of the client's during handshake.
3	Your GraphQL requests can use your Spec Hub schemas for autocomplete suggestions.
3	Runs after each HTTP response. Generally used to write tests and visualize responses.
3	Make sure the Desktop Agent is installed and check your toolbar to see if it's running.
3	Runs before each HTTP request is sent. Generally used to configure requests dynamically.
3	This temporary body parameter is generated by Postman and is not saved with your request.
3	Order of cipher suites that the SSL server profile uses to establish a secure connection.
3	Runs after a response is received. Use it to write tests and set up a response visualizer.
3	Access and reuse requests easily by saving them to a collection. Tip: Use ⌘S for quick saving.
3	Redirect with the original HTTP method instead of the default behavior of redirecting with GET.
3	Test generation needs a response from the server. Send the request to get a response and try again.
3	Runs before the request is sent. Use it to create API workflows by configuring the request dynamically.
3	Requests can't be sent in public workspaces right now – though we're working on that for a future release!
3	Verify SSL certificates when sending a request. Verification failures will result in the request being aborted.
3	Specify the SSL and TLS protocol versions to be disabled during handshake. All other protocols will be enabled.
3	This setting is using the value set in global settings. Changing this setting will override it for this request.
3	Certain settings aren't available with the Interceptor Agent. Switch to the Desktop agent to customize your requests further.
3	Creating a new tab automatically selects the last created request type to make it easier for you to work with multiple API technologies.
3	Prevent cookies used in this request from being stored in the cookie jar. Existing cookies in the cookie jar will not be added as headers for this request.
3	This file isn't in your working directory. Teammates you share this request with won't be able to use this file. To make collaboration easier you can setup your working directory in Settings.
2	Unwrap Lines
2	Linear Chart
2	All messages
2	Change agent
2	Ready to go!
2	Proposed fix
2	Save response
2	Share example
2	Copy response
2	Click to copy
2	Delete example
2	No match found
2	Update example
2	Clear response
2	Clear messages
2	Generate Tests
2	View in console
2	View Next Steps
2	Next suggestion
2	Send the request
2	Set up visualizer
2	Search in response
2	Toggle schema view
2	Visualize Response
2	Fix script with AI
2	Dismiss suggestion
2	Organize collection
2	Enter Response Code
2	All systems are go!
2	The coast is clear!
2	Suggestion settings
2	Previous suggestion
2	Try with Agent Mode
2	Show AI suggestions
2	Toggle line wrapping
2	Set up with a prompt
2	You're all caught up
2	Save response to file
2	Refresh Visualization
2	Proactive suggestions
2	Toggle response filter
2	No anomalies detected!
2	View security warnings 
2	Standing by for launch!
2	Looking for a suggestion…
2	Use Postman's Desktop Agent
2	And I refuse to brew coffee!
2	Increase response size limit
2	Response copied to clipboard
2	Toggle visualization options
2	Proactive request suggestions
2	Need help with the next steps?
2	That wasn't supposed to happen.
2	Visualize response with Postbot
2	I found a fix for this request.
2	Response exceeded the 5 MB limit
2	Try filtering on a different key
2	Generating script with Postbot...
2	Something's wrong and no idea what.
2	No cookies received from the server
2	Desktop Agent version not supported
2	Learn about troubleshooting requests
2	All size calculations are approximate
2	Save this request to create examples.
2	Close the stream to save the response.
2	Close the stream to clear the response.
2	Identifies a specific resource version.
2	This needs a closer look in Agent Mode.
2	A new resource was created successfully.
2	Reset the document that sent this request.
2	Close the stream to download the response.
2	No tests available for the selected filter
2	Everything alright. Proceed with the request.
2	Response body is too large to generate table.
2	Request is too large for the server to process.
2	Responses over 5 MB can't be saved as examples.
2	Fetching active environment and sending request
2	Response body is too large to generate preview.
2	Headers are too large for the server to process.
2	Organize your growing collection with Postman AI
2	Sends cookies from the server to the user agent.
2	Access to the requested resource requires payment.
2	Processing the response. No response available yet.
2	The request was well-formed but had semantic errors.
2	Filtered data exceeds 50 MB. Try refining the filter.
2	Redirected to another URL for the requested resource.
2	That's too long a URI and the server is not having it.
2	The request failed due to failure of a previous request.
2	The client needs to authenticate to gain network access.
2	Request successful. The server has responded as required.
2	Use of the request method is not allowed on the resource.
2	Requested content is permanently deleted from the server.
2	Control where Agent Mode surfaces contextual suggestions.
2	Display fix and improvement suggestions in the status bar.
2	Part of the resource is received as per the 'Range' header.
2	This request is linked and doesn't support saving examples.
2	Saving response body to file requires body to not be empty.
2	The connection was closed before the timeout period elapsed.
2	The 'X-Forwarded-For' header contains too many IP addresses.
2	The web hosting service has exceeded the available bandwidth.
2	An unsecured (HTTP) request was sent to a secured (HTTPS) port.
2	All your cookies and their associated domains will appear here.
2	There is no content to send for this request except for headers.
2	There's an error between Cloudflare and origin's railgun server.
2	Request to 'upgrade' the connection received. Switching protocol.
2	Either the request or some headers are too large to be processed.
2	There seems to be an invalid character in the response header value
2	The connection was closed before the server could complete the task.
2	The HTTP version used in the request is not supported by the server.
2	Make sure the request URL, variables, and other attributes are valid.
2	There seems to be an invalid character in response header key or value
2	Linked requests only support overrides on the request name and params.
2	Specifying the form of encoding used to transfer the entity to the user.
2	This is a situation that calls for multiple status codes. One isn't enough.
2	The request was directed at a server that is unable to send back a response.
2	Further extensions to the request are required for the server to fulfill it.
2	Once you send this request, Postman AI can help you with recommended next steps
2	The request method is not supported by the server and thus could not be handled.
2	The request couldn't be processed because it doesn't contain the required information.
2	You've reached the monthly usage limit of Cloud Agent calls. Select a different agent.
2	Request could not be processed because too many requests have been sent in a given time.
2	The request conflicts with the current state of the server. So, it could not be processed.
2	The response has not been modified. Continue using the same cached version of the response.
2	There has been a connection timeout behind the proxy to a HTTP client in front of the proxy.
2	There has been a network read timeout behind the proxy to a HTTP client in front of the proxy.
2	Used in preflight requests. Tells the server what HTTP method will be used in the actual request.
2	Used in preflight requests. Tells the server what HTTP headers will be used in the actual request.
2	Used in response to a preflight request. Specifies which method or methods can access the resource.
2	Identifies Ajax requests. Most JavaScript frameworks send this header with value of XMLHttpRequest.
2	Identifies the protocol (HTTP or HTTPS) that a client used to connect to your proxy or load balancer.
2	Security warnings indicate that there are potential security risks that your API might be vulnerable to.
2	Used in response to a preflight request. Specifies which HTTP headers can be used in the actual request.
2	This is an indication for the client to start pre-loading resources while the server is preparing a response.
2	Request is taking longer than 30 seconds to fulfill. Use another agent to send a request without time limitations.
2	Identifies the originating IP address of a client connecting to a web server through an HTTP proxy or load balancer.
2	Added by proxies and used to track message forwards, avoid request loops and identify protocol capabilities of senders.
2	You're using an older version of Postman Desktop Agent which does not support this request. Update the Desktop Agent and try again.
1	Think harder
1	Open Passport settings
1	Your access was revoked.
1	Enabled but host/port is not configured.
1	mTLS handshake failed. Reconnect Passport.
1	Your certificate expired. Reconnect Passport.
1	Your access was revoked. Reconnect Passport and try again.
1	Too many requests through the proxy. Please retry shortly.
1	Your certificate is missing identity info. Reconnect Passport.
1	Your certificate isn't trusted by the proxy. Reconnect Passport.
1	Your certificate is missing. Re-enable Secured Access Proxy in settings.
1	Linked requests only support overrides on the request name, params, scripts, and body.
